This is Ranma from the Saotome
School of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
And this is Akane of the Tendo Dojo.
These two teens were arranged
to be married by their parents.
Don't tell me what to do!
You're so annoying.
Unfortunately,
Ranma has a bit of a problem.
Hmm?
What the hell was that?
When he's splashed with cold water,
he transforms into a girl.
RANMA1/2
SHAMPOO CLEANS UP
The Kiss of Death.
I'll hunt you down to the depths of hell,
and kill you.
Oh, don't worry,
'cause I'm not going anywhere.
I'm putting an end to this here.
Akane!
Akane! Akane! Akane!
Hey.
Akane!
Huh?
What happened?
Do I know you?
Of course you do!
Now what happened between you and Shampoo?
Shampoo...
Uh, Akane?
I remember...
I think I was trying to fight Shampoo.
But what happened after that?
Somehow, my head feels
much more refreshed now.
Hey, Akane. Wait for me.
Uh, you're acting
like I should know you or something.
What?
Who even are you?
Oh, come on...
Hmm?
Sorry, did you and I
meet somewhere before?
Huh?
Hmm.
Wait. No way.
Is it amnesia?
Look! There she is.
Akane!
Oh. Hey, you guys.
We were all worried about you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm totally fine.
Was that Shampoo girl a tough opponent?
I didn't think she was that bad.
Right, P-chan?
You can't be serious right now.
She knocked you out cold.
Again, who even are you?
Oh, please!
Do you know this guy?
He a transfer student?
Huh? What do you mean?
Akane?
Uh...
So, he's my fiancé?
Yeah. You've lived together
for quite a while now.
- It's Ranma!
- Mm-hmm.
There's no way
you're telling me the truth.
Wait. Ranma?
Ran-ma...
Ranma?
Huh? Now that I think about it,
it does sound kinda familiar.
For some weird reason,
it makes me feel nostalgic.
- Akane?
- What's the matter?
That's a lattice or openwork
installed between the lintel and ceiling
to provide ventilation
and lighting, isn't it?
You're thinking of a ranma.
A Latin music of Cuban origin in 2/4 time
with a strong, dynamic beat!
Now you're thinking of a rumba!
What is this?
I'm the only thing she's forgotten about!
I need you to come with me.
Hang on. What are you doing with P-chan?
We're just having a conversation.
Give him back!
Okay.
He moves too well to be just anyone.
Who was the guy that ran away?
I already told you it's Ranma.
Hup, two, three, four!
Hup, two, three, four! Hup!
Tell me everything you saw
in the fight earlier.
What move did Shampoo pull on Akane?
Let me just take a second
to make sure I've got this straight.
You think I'll help Akane remember you?
You bastard!
From where I stand, the way
things are playing out right now
is actually pretty convenient for me.
Uh...
- Hey, ladies!
- ...four!
You wanna see somethin' cool?
Shut the door, you ass!
Anyway, I'm getting goose bumps
just thinking about it.
I mean, the way Shampoo moved her legs...
And that's all I saw.
You know,
you could've saved us some time
and said you didn't see anything.
OSTEOPATHIC CLINIC-CHIROPRACTOR
ACUPUNCTURE-ACUPRESSURE
Hmm.
I don't see an external injury.
How did you feel
after you regained consciousness?
Well, I guess it felt
like my head was refreshed.
Huh. I see.
So do you know what it is, Dr. Tofu?
A legendary attack.
The Demon Fist, Xi Fa Shiang Gao Shiatsu.
Huh? What the hell is that?
Huh?
YOU'RE RIGHT!
Oh. Mr. Saotome.
Hang on. You saw the fight, Pops?
THE WHOLE SHEBANG!
Hurry up and turn back into a human!
EVEN NOW AS I...
Oh, it was incredible.
I mean, thinking back on it,
it was quite clear.
This was a divine technique.
The movement of her hands
after slipping behind her opponent
was unlike anything I've ever seen.
It took only 56 seconds
for the whole shampoo, cut and blowout!
Amazing.
So that explains
why my head felt refreshed.
Right. What exactly is this technique?
Xi Fa Shiang Gao Shiatsu
is quite esoteric.
Its user needs to have
a specially blended shampoo.
Then, the fearsome technique
uses pressure points on the head
to manipulate the victim's memory.
Oh! That must be why
you don't remember me at all.
Who are you again?
Is there any way we can cure this?
First off, we'll need to get our hands on
that shampoo she used on you.
All right. Come on, Akane.
What's happening?
Shampoo! Hey!
- Where are you?
- What the hell is wrong with you?
Give me the shampoo!
Shampoo!
I have returned.
Hello.
Also, this is the new apprentice nurse.
Shampoo will now be living here
as a tenant.
SMALL WORLD... ISN'T IT?
I'm home now.
Akane!
I heard that you don't remember Ranma
anymore.
Ranma? Who is that again?
Put it to you this way.
Who's that guy standing behind you?
Right there.
Huh?
Hey! What makes you think you have
the right to follow me into my house?
Uh, well, I kinda live here.
Oh, wow.
So she really forgot all about him, huh?
Everything is going to be
just fine, Akane.
That is as long as you haven't forgotten
about me, of course.
Who are you, Mister?
Dad, I was just kidding.
You don't have to cry.
Yeah, she's doin' okay.
Damn it.
Where could Shampoo have run off to?
GUESS WHO?
Why did you do that,
you crazy old ma...
HOO HOO! HE FELL FOR IT!
You fell for it!
Shampoo, you're being such a...
Wo de ai ren.
What are you doing?
Uh, so who are you again?
You're telling me...
I don't understand what happened.
The moment I saw the two of them hugging,
I lost my temper.
An unconscious reflex.
Somewhere deep down inside of her heart,
she still remembers Ranma.
Hang on. Are you that thing
we put on top of ramen?
Now you're thinking of menma.
My technique
must not have been fully effective.
She's a formidable woman.
So I'll just try again!
Xi Fa Shiang Gao Shiatsu!
Okay.
Now that I've gotten this shampoo...
Ai ren!
Ow, ow, ow, that hurts!
What do you think you're doing?
That shampoo won't work, Ranma.
Trust me.
You're in on this, Doctor?
Just take a look
at the blend number printed on the bottle.
It's one, one, zero.
If our aim is to recover her lost memory,
you need to find a bottle
with blend number 119 printed on it.
Mm-hmm.
Well, where do I get that?
There's no need to worry.
We can find the formula in this book.
Wonderful, Doctor!
So Akane can be cured with that, right?
Oh, Kasumi.
It's so good to see you,
but what are you doing here?
Doctor, you're the one
who came to my house.
Oh, right, it's your house.
Okay, I get it now--
Why are you tearing it up
if we need that?
So what's happened this time
that's making you pack up, Ranma?
I thought it was pretty obvious.
I'm going to a drugstore in China
to buy shampoo 119.
Yay!
Bring me back a souvenir, okay?
HOW ABOUT SOME GRECIAN FORMULA?
- ...oolong tea.
- ...some Shanghai crab...
- ...all the cigarettes you can...
- ...some rice crackers...
I don't get it. Why is this guy
so desperate to help me?
Hey, Akane.
Just wait for me.
You're definitely gonna remember me
by the end of this.
Oh, Ranma, my boy!
Thank you so much...
BRINGS A TEAR TO YOUR EYE,
DON'T IT?
There's no need to hold back.
Say it with your chest!
Oh, man.
I don't know what it is about him...
but it makes me want to remember
who he is.
Now I just need to figure out
how to get to China for free.
I'll probably have to swim there
like I did with Dad the last time.
It's not gonna be easy,
but I don't have a choice.
That's the only way
I can get the 119 stuff.
Whoa!
Hmm?
One, one, nine?
Gimme that!
Wait right there. Shampoo!
Hmm?
Huh?
Come get it.
You think something like this
is gonna scare me out of a challenge?
You might not believe it, but
I'm very familiar with the female body!
So I'm getting what I want!
Ah! Not like that! I'm sorry!
Fine! Why don't we try this, then?
I owe you a massive favor.
Whatever you want.
You mean it?
On my honor as a man.
I'll do anything but the limit is that you
can't ask me to kill Akane or marry you.
Fine.
Huh?
The girl Ranma. Kill her instead.
DOJO ENTRANCE THIS WAY
Just so I'm clear,
Shampoo doesn't get that you
and female Ranma are the same person?
Nope. I'm pretty sure she does not.
If you end female Ranma's life for me,
I give you shampoo 119 in return.
Do we have a deal?
Yeah. I gotcha.
But do you think we could settle
for a half-kill?
I don't understand
what that means, but okay.
So, yeah, that about covers it.
Ryoga, I want you to beat me up.
I'm not doing that.
You should accept reality
and let me be the one
to take care of Akane.
This could be the starting point
of our blossoming love! Mmm.
Ranma? Who is that again?
Ha! He's not worth remembering, my sweet.
I'm politely asking you to help.
And I already told you no!
Come on, let's keep this going.
I've been begging you to beat me up.
Then I'll beat you to death!
Yeah, now you're gettin' it!
Oh, you idiot.
You weren't supposed to collapse yet!
How am I supposed to recover
Akane's memory
if you don't beat the crap out of me?
We can be the ones to help!
IT'S ALL SO SWEET!
It just means so much
that you'd go this far for Akane, Ranma!
What are you doing?
Akane. Look!
Look at this man and be amazed!
It's a monster!
Who you callin' a monster?
Well, what the heck are you then?
Hmm?
Hyah!
Dad! You know you shouldn't be
picking on weaklings.
So I'll fight you in his place.
Hey...
- Hmm?
- Stay out of this, you idiot.
Why should I?
Oh, come on!
Who do you think I'm getting beat up for
in the first place?
Mmm?
I don't know why I'm surprised.
This is why you're not cute!
Not cute! ...cute! ...cute!
So I'm not cute?
Hmm?
- Huh...
- Mmm?
Ah. Hold on.
Ranma, say that again.
You're not cute!
Say it again!
She's responding.
Onward, Ranma! Break through to her
with your soul-stirring words!
Well, if that's what you want, I got this.
You're not sexy. You're a
vicious, klutzy dork that's totally flat!
You bastard!
How dare you
throw those awful words at Akane?
Oh, great. You're still alive.
You're not cute!
You're not cute.
You're not sexy. This isn't sexy.
Not very sexy.
That's not sexy!
You're not sexy.
You're not sexy!
You're not sexy! You're not sexy...
What the hell is wrong with you, Ranma?
Akane! You remembered him! Ranma!
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm! The miracle of love.
You're heavy.
Huh?
- Ah!
- Hello.
Shampoo?
Ah! Ai ren?
- Ai ren!
- Whoa!
Hmm?
So, you've remembered Ranma.
You are a persistent one.
Yeah, well, right back at you!
Then I have no choice.
If you didn't remember him,
you wouldn't have to die!
Shampoo, stop this.
Wo ai ni.
Just hang on a second.
You promised.
You said you wouldn't hurt Akane.
Remove the obstacle.
It's the natural order of things.
There's no choice.
I have to tell you the truth.
You female Ranma?
Yeah. Coming out like this is hard.
But the male form is just temporary.
Check 'em out. I've been hiding
that I'm actually a girl.
I HAD NO IDEA!
So, yeah, I guess
my relationship with you is, uh...
Die!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Mmm.
Bié le.
Shampoo.
"Bié le."
It's the Chinese word for "farewell."
Which I'm guessing means
that you'll never see that girl again.
You know, it's never too late.
You should turn back into a man
and stop her.
Oh, shut up.
Still, it's kind of a waste to let her go.